{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.5.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":2790,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":31,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":true,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si16785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16796","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16805","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16808","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5184","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16785","si16796","Text_Caption_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5184"}}},{"id":"si16868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16877","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_7","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16856","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16868","Text_Caption_26","Text_Caption_27","Image_1","Text_Caption_28","Image_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16856"}}},{"id":"si17037","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_9","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16961","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17037","Text_Caption_35","Image_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16961"}}},{"id":"si17153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_10","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17152","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17153","Text_Caption_36","Image_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17152"}}},{"id":"si17232","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17241","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17244","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_12","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17168","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17232","Text_Caption_40","Image_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17168"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_14","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17322","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17322"}}},{"id":"si17558","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17567","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17570","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_16","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_16","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17485","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17558","Text_Caption_52","Image_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17485"}}},{"id":"si17711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17720","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17723","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_4","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_17","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_18","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17710","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17711","Text_Caption_53","Image_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17710"}}},{"id":"si17825","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17834","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17837","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_18","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_20","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17824","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17825","Text_Caption_54","Image_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17824"}}},{"id":"si17937","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17946","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si17949","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_6","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_19","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_22","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17936","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17937","Text_Caption_55","Image_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17936"}}},{"id":"si18051","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18060","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18063","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_7","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_20","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_24","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18050","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18051","Text_Caption_56","Image_24"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18050"}}},{"id":"si18167","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18176","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18179","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_8","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_21","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_25","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18166","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18167","Text_Caption_58","Image_25"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18166"}}},{"id":"si18272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18281","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18284","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_9","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_22","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_27","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18271","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18272","Text_Caption_59","Image_27"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18271"}}},{"id":"si18384","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18393","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18396","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_10","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_23","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_29","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18383","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18384","Text_Caption_60","Image_29"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18383"}}},{"id":"si18495","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18504","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18507","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_11","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_24","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_31","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18494","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18495","Text_Caption_61","Image_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18494"}}},{"id":"si18607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18616","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18619","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_12","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_25","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_33","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18606","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18607","Text_Caption_62","Image_33"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18606"}}},{"id":"si18719","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18728","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18731","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_13","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_26","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_35","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18718","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18719","Text_Caption_63","Image_35"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18718"}}},{"id":"si18831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18840","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18843","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_14","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_27","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_37","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"interactionId":"","quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18830","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18831","Text_Caption_64","Image_37"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18830"}}},{"id":"si18943","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18952","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si18955","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_15","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_28","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_39","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18942","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si18943","Text_Caption_65","Image_39"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18942"}}},{"id":"si19050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19062","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_29","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19118","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19132","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19209","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19235","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_43","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19013","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19050","Text_Caption_66","Button_1","si19118","si19132","Button_2","si19209","si19235","Image_43"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19013"}}},{"id":"si19802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19909","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19829","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19836","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19843","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19855","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19855","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19851_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Memorizing all employee laws\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19862","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19866","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19862_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Not being consistent with statements to the state agencies\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":5}}}},{"id":"si19940","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19944","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19944","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19940_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dictating accommodations\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":5}}}},{"id":"si19955","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19959","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19959","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19955_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Firing employees too fast\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":5}}}},{"id":"si19913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19792q0","for":"Slide19792q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19870","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19896","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19792q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19792","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19802","si19829","si19836","si19855","si19866","si19944","si19959","si19913","si19896"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19792"},"question":{"interactionId":"19816","quizId":378,"title":"Multiple Select\r","text":"Which mistakes might a manager make that could cause a lawsuit?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B","C","D"],"score":{"weight":15,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si19973","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19963q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20080","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si20000","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20007","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20014","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si20022","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20022_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Because it looks suspicious and inconsistent.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si20033","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20037","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20033_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It is ok to over document the final days of a tenure so it is not a mistake.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20105","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20109","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20105_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Because performance logs are not valid in a court case.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20120","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20120_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Because managers duties do not include keep a record of employee conduct.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19963q1","for":"Slide19963q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20041","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19963q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19963q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20067","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19963q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19963","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19973","si20000","si20007","si20026","si20037","si20109","si20124","si20084","si20067"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19963"},"question":{"interactionId":"19987","quizId":378,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Papering an employee’s file right before a firing is a mistake that managers make which could harm an organization’s credibility in court. Why?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":15,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21177","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21284","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si21204","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21211","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21218","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si21226","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21230","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21230","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21226_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Interview errors\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":15}}}},{"id":"si21237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21241","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21241","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21237_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Inaccurate performance reviews\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21444","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21448","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21448","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21444_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sloppy documentation\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21463","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21463","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21459_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Lack of legal knowledge\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21288","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21167q2","for":"Slide21167q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21245","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21271","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21522","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21167q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21167","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21177","si21204","si21211","si21230","si21241","si21448","si21463","si21288","si21271"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21167"},"question":{"interactionId":"21191","quizId":378,"title":"Multiple Select\r","text":"Which mistakes were discussed in the lesson?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","D"],"score":{"weight":15,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21312","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21419","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si21339","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21346","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21353","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si21361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21365","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21365","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21361_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sugarcoat your words to employees\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21376","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21372_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Keep employement logs\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":15}}}},{"id":"si21474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21478","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21478","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21474_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use the golden rule when handling staff\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21493","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21493","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21489_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Take notes on a person’s resume\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21423","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21302q3","for":"Slide21302q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21380","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21393","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22067","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21302q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21302","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21312","si21339","si21346","si21365","si21376","si21478","si21493","si21423","si21406"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21302"},"question":{"interactionId":"21326","quizId":378,"title":"Multiple Select\r","text":"Select tips that managers should do to avoid lawsuits.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B","C"],"score":{"weight":15,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si20138","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20128q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20245","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si20165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20172","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20179","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si20187","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20191","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20187_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20202","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20198_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20249","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20128q4","for":"Slide20128q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20206","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20128q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20219","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20128q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20232","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20128q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20128","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20138","si20165","si20172","si20191","si20202","si20249","si20232"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20128"},"question":{"interactionId":"20152","quizId":378,"title":"True/False","text":"During an interview, you can ask a candidate if he/she has children and appropriate daycare. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si20478","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20477q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","roles":{}},{"id":"si20291","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20303","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20336","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1","roles":{}},{"id":"si20314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20314_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20325_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20467","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20477q5","for":"Slide20477q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20367","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20477q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20477q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20477q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20477","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20478","si20291","si20303","si20318","si20329","si20467","si20429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20477"},"question":{"interactionId":"20277","quizId":378,"title":"True/False","text":"Making comments like “boys will be boys” or “I’m not your babysitter” are okay comments to make to employees.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si20930","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20929q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20887","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","roles":{}},{"id":"si20743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20755","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{}},{"id":"si20766","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20770","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20766_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20781","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20777_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"9","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20929q6","for":"Slide20929q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20819","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20929q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20850","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20929q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20881","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20929q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20929","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20930","si20743","si20755","si20770","si20781","si20919","si20881"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20929"},"question":{"interactionId":"20729","quizId":378,"title":"True/False","text":"Performance reviews are one of the most important form of documentation.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21156","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21155q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","roles":{}},{"id":"si20969","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20981","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_7","roles":{}},{"id":"si20992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20996","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20992_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7_10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21003","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21003_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"9_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21155q7","for":"Slide21155q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21045","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21155q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21076","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21155q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21155q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21155","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21156","si20969","si20981","si20996","si21007","si21145","si21107"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21155"},"question":{"interactionId":"20955","quizId":378,"title":"True/False","text":"Emails are not considered a form of documentation when used in a court of law.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si19253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19275","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19283","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19291","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19299","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19307","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19264","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19271","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19279","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19287","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19303","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19311","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19315","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19243","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19243"}}},{"id":"si19381","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19401","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19404","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_30","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_44","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19380","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Fail","thumbnail":"","children":["si19381","si19392","Text_Caption_68","Image_44","Text_Caption_69"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19380"}}},{"id":"si19760","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19771","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19780","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si19783","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_31","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_46","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19759","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Pass","thumbnail":"","children":["si19760","si19771","Text_Caption_70","Text_Caption_71","Image_46"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19759"}}},{"id":"Pool422","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":422,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"DirtyDozen","class":"project","title":"DirtyDozen","children":["Slide5184","Slide16856","Slide16961","Slide17152","Slide17168","Slide17322","Slide17485","Slide17710","Slide17824","Slide17936","Slide18050","Slide18166","Slide18271","Slide18383","Slide18494","Slide18606","Slide18718","Slide18830","Slide18942","Slide19013","Slide19792","Slide19963","Slide21167","Slide21302","Slide20128","Slide20477","Slide20929","Slide21155","Slide19243","Slide19380","Slide19759"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":378,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["Slide19792q0","Slide19963q1","Slide21167q2","Slide21302q3","Slide20128q4","Slide20477q5","Slide20929q6","Slide21155q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":100,"passScore":70}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":false,"close":false,"mute":false,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"view","CCData":{"viewDataIsPercent":true,"viewData":100},"SCCriteria":"view","SCData":{"viewDataIsPercent":true,"viewData":100},"exitNormalIfCompleted":true},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5184","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide16856","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide16961","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide17152","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide17168","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide17322","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide17485","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17710","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17824","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide17936","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide18050","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide18166","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide18271","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide18383","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide18494","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide18606","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide18718","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide18830","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide18942","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide19013","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide19792","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide19963","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide21167","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide21302","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide20128","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide20477","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide20929","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide21155","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide19243","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide19380","title":"Fail"},{"id":"Slide19759","title":"Pass"}]}